<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<!-- ZATON STASHES -->
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_57">
		<text>Allright, just get that cannon away from me. The stash is near the Zaton ranger Station, but you'll have to climb on a roof and walk some pipes to get there. Personally, I think its not worth it, but it's your decision.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_58">
		<text>Do you like the smell of your own flesh burning? You are about to get that a lot since I stashed that shit inside a chimney in that burning hell hole of a farm in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_59">
		<text>I will talk, no more, please calm the fuck down. The dredge station in Zaton has my loot, it's right there, waiting for your greasy hands.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_60">
		<text>It was right under everyones nose the whole time. Have you ever checked out the view on top of the Skadovsk? Hidden on top of that old beast, is my gift to you, because you made me realize I don't need any of this shit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_61">
		<text>You know that crazy bastard that lives with a mutant dog? Well my stash is on the giant crane and you can use the anomaly on top of that old rusty ship to get there. I'm sure you could just walk right in there from the front door.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_62">
		<text>A friend of mine went insane and next thing I see, he's running on all four like a beast. The roof of the gas station in Zaton is where my stash is. That place is full of snorks. If you see my friend there, please spare the bullets and run.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_63">
		<text>What now? You want to take everything I have right? Rob me blind? Why would you give a fuck. But you are the boss now, the big man with the gun on my head, travel to the Waste Processing Station in Zaton, it's behind a building there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_64">
		<text>Just leave me be, I've got so much to live for. I haven't even seen my daughter back home. Just take everything I have, it's in a stash behind a building in Zaton's Waste Processing Station.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_65">
		<text>Listen, you could kill me right here. Splatter my brains all over, but you'd loose then. Why? Well because I know of a stash. Oh now you don't really want to kill me huh? Go inside the Waste Processing Station. Figure it out from there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_66">
		<text>The Americans said that the bridge was impossible to stand tall for long, it seems the architect B.N. Preobrazhensky didn't build the bridge "bomb proof". I hid my stash east of the bridge in Zaton, look for it in thick bushes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_67">
		<text>Just keep that shooter away from my face. I'll spill the beans, you won fair and square. I have to say, you are quite good at hunting people Stalker. Head north of the Burnt Farmstead and search behind some rocks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_68">
		<text>I've been trying to save so I can finally get out of this shit hole. As much as I hate Zaton, I won't last 3 hours in Yanov, I'm not going to even mention Pripyat. This stash is my last hope of ever getting out of here man. But you take it if you have to, it is in the Ranger station in Zaton, below a top window.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_69">
		<text>My mother was a tough broad and a good person. My father on the other hand was the worst kind of scum in the world. He didn't beat us with a belt, because he wanted to feel, with his hands, when he beat us. He was a drunk gambling monster. I lost all fear of death when I was younger because of that man. When my mom lost her job, my dad got insanely more aggressive as the days went by. I still send them money. But you don't care, you just want my stash right? It's on top of the huge crane in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_70">
		<text>I know you are in a hard position here, all of us are fighting for survival. But lets be practical. Imagine if everyone was shooting and killing each other, how could you kill a Chimera with a one man team? Who would bring in more ammo? We depend on each other. Just don't shoot, and here, take my stash, it's in the tunnel close to the downed chopper.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_71">
		<text> I knew this would happen, I knew some bitch like you will one day "politely" ask for my stash. So you know what I did? I made it so stealing my stash would be living fucking hell for you. You can find the stash in the Iron Forrest. Search for a dark corner, until you feel the surge of electricity. Feel free to die right then and there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_73">
		<text>You shit fucker. You whore bitch. I will rape your mother. I would've put a bullet to your head, if I was a bit faster. Just take the stash and die. It's in Zaton, the north west forest, behind some big rocks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_72">
		<text>Now that I think about it, maybe I have some goodies for you north of the Burnt Farmstead in Zaton. Look behind some rocks there, consider this a farewell gift, also if I might add: "please don't kill me afterwards".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_74">
		<text>Do you have any idea who I am? Get that fucking thing away from my eyes. If you shoot me, a hailstorm of bullets will rain on your head. Just take the stash in the hall above the tunnel in Zaton, it's not even mine, some fool begged me not to kill him and gave me his stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_75">
		<text>I have loot, I have a stash, don't shoot. Stay calm, I mean you no harm. I was jittery and I started shooting, the Zone does that to a person. My fault entirely. Get to the large wall in Zaton and what's mine is yours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_76">
		<text>Bushes, nobody checks in the bushes. Well I do, and I hide shit there. You can enjoy what I've earned through sweat and blood in there, they are at the very back in Zaton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_77">
		<text>Are you a good climber? You can cash in on that stash if you carefully inspect the branches in this tree in Zaton. I hope you break your neck while climbing there but feel free to take whatever you need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_78">
		<text>My idiot brother got shot in a very similar situation because he didn't reveal our stash. I'm not doing the same mistake. Go behind a cement pillar close to the wall in Zaton and take everything. My life is worth more than that damn stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_79">
		<text>Woah hello there, what a pleasant way to meet a new friend. The last person I met like this is now my best friend because I showed him a great stash to raid. Go behind a cement pillar in the dam in Zaton and see for yourself what a good friend I am.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_80">
		<text>Don't shoot, please don't shoot, I surrender and I'm not armed. You don't want to shoot me do you? You seem like a good enough fellow, so I will share my stash location in regards to these rescent circuimstances we have here. It's right under the iron bridge in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_81">
		<text>You want my stash, just don't shoot, we both loose if you shoot. I'm a mutant hunter, I make sure their numbers are in check. My stash is hidden in the bushes next to the huge boulder.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_82">
		<text>So I've become the prey huh? I see no problem with that, and you should shoot if you have to, but I have a tasty stash for you in a container on Shevchenko in Zaton, but you could shoot me anyway right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_83">
		<text>No, shit, no. I was careless. One time I relax, this one time, and here you are, holding a gun to my head. In the hopes of offering a remedy to this situation, I offer my stash that is placed high above the ground, behind the Water Plant in good old Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_90">
		<text>Behind some metal fences in a dark corner in the basement over at Zaton, I had a sizeable amount of stuff you might be interested. If you like it, take it, if not, I will be waiting here, you could shoot me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_91">
		<text>I was forced to come here, in this piece of shit hell. My mother said: "You will go and bring money back". But you could also take the money, my family is a bunch of assholes. It's in the last toilet in the back, in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_92">
		<text>I hid something of interest to you, in a dark room in the basement. In exchange for you not ending my life, I will hand all my possession in that stash to you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_93">
		<text>You look like a decent human being, you are a good person, don't do this. My stash is hidden in the floor at the entrance, take it. Take whatever you can find, and leave in peace.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_94">
		<text>Please. My stash. In small house behind box in Zaton. Please don't. Please.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_95">
		<text>In a large bush among many trees in Zaton, I hid everything that I have accumulated while being here. Take it, but keep in mind that it is literally everything I have, and you will leave me with nothing to survive in this Zone. Beats a bullet to the head though.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_96">
		<text>What you need to relax is some loot. Am I right? Do I have your attention now? There is a merc backpack in the Water Plant in Zaton that has your name on it, it used to have my name, but things change quickly in the Zone, and your gun is very persuasive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_97">
		<text>I'm sick of this, I don't want to fight anymore. Fuck this place with an iron rod. Take my stash that is stored between the wall and a container, I'm done with everything here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_98">
		<text>I'm very sorry for shooting at you, it's the Zone, anyone can be the enemy. You could fix yourself up with the drugs stored in the rooms of Shevchenko in Zaton. Think of it as a gift of peace. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_99">
		<text>There is also drugs stored in the main room of Shevchenko in Zaton if you are so persistent. Just grab them and leave me be, I have other more important things to attend to.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_100">
		<text>You like to party with the Zombies? On the roof next to the chimney at Sawmill in Zaton you could find my stash, and a bunch of, how to put it… "barely people" to party with, have your fun there, and don't forget, I'm always much more interesting alive than dead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_101">
		<text>On the first floor in the Ranger Station you will find a stash I was preparing to send back to my daughter in my home town. Her step mom could sell water to a drowning victim, and would make good use of that stash, but I guess you could also take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_102">
		<text>Get a sniper, get at least 20 bullets, 10 if you are a sharpshooter, and clean the old Sawmill in Zaton out of Zombies. Then you could climb on top of the tractor and claim your reward, or just sneak in.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_103">
		<text>Dig around the motors in the lower front of Shechenko, you are bound to find some of my well hidden loot there, take it and watch your back, because I'm going to be your shadow for a while from now on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_104">
		<text>The gas station in Zaton has an underground area, besides some nasty critters, there you could also find my stash that I hid, before those critters populated that place. Now would you consider not raping my brain with that canon?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_105">
		<text>Stash, you want my stash, everyone wants my stash, but you have the gun now, so you are getting my stash. It's well hidden in an elevator shaft that is locked up in Zaton. Do your worst.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_zat_hiding_place_106">
		<text>I left my rucksack behind the building near the teleporter anomaly on the way from Zaton to Jupiter. I don't have much, so please, at least leave my photo of my wife. It's all I have left of her...</text>
	</string>
	<!-- JUPITER STASHES -->
<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_51">
		<text>How about I give you something, and you give me my life back? There is a little something for you inside the wheel of that monstrous quarry machine in Jupiter. We have a deal?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_52">
		<text>Shit I can't look at that shooter any more. Just go take my stash, clean it out and leave me the fuck alone. Climb High on top of the Jupiter plant. Outside is what you need. Are we done now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_53">
		<text>I'm done, I'm done with it all. This Zone just takes a piece of you, every single time. Take my stash, take my fucking life, this is bullshit. Behind the table in the first room is everything I've ever had, besides my life.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_54">
		<text>Listen, this is unnecessary. People get into brawls all the time here, it doesn't mean you have to blow my brains right? Just go behind the small building. near the Jupiter Plant. Outside is what will make you not pull that trigger you are itching to scratch.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_55">
		<text>You like climbing? You better be fit for some acrobatics because my stash is well hidden high above the ground. Check the Jupiter Plant, over at the corner. Careful not to slip up, but if you do, you'd better off yourself right there. Getting your intestines ravaged by those screaming rats is a much worse experience than a quick bullet.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_56">
		<text>Hi there, we haven't been properly introduced. I usually don't shoot at people but you looked quite menacing. As a token of my gratitude for you not indulging yourself in ending my life, go and scavenge a bit right next to the chopper in a corner in Jupiter. You will like what you find. It's right next to that metal shelf.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_57">
		<text>Next to the chopper in Jupiter, you will find the reason not to rape my face with that canon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_58">
		<text>Confession time already? Well ok then. Forgive me father for I have sinned. I've murdered, stole and sold my friends. I'm not going to go into what I've done to my enemies. My stash is stored on top of the truck. in the huge hall of Jupiter. Are my sins now forgiven?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_59">
		<text>I was a trashman back home. I have absolutely no trouble digging in nasty piles of trash. If you want to find my stash, go to the Train Sub Station in Jupiter. Against the wall there is a nice pile of garbage that hides underneath some goodies for you. You could also not kill me, while you are at it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_60">
		<text>The Cement factory in Jupiter, on the first floor of the building. That's what you are after right? Unless you are just torturing me for no freaking reason, and I just gave you my most valuables for no reason.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_61">
		<text>Save those bullets for the Zombies in the Cement factory in Jupiter. That's where my stash is. Outside in a concrete block. I'd shoot them bastards in the head or spine if I were you. Also if I were you, I would let me be right about now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_62">
		<text>This is twice, twice today that someone is holding a gun at my head. Am I supposed to give you my other stash now? Just don't start blasting, it's in the open, under the fallen tree in good old Jupiter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_63">
		<text>This was a shitty day from the start. Got shitfaced on Vodka because I took some rads in from an old metal wreck, a pack of dogs chased me for 3 kilometers, and now this. One step at a time I guess. My stash is on the roof of the shelter at tunnel opening in Jupiter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_64">
		<text>What a nice shooter you have there? Did you get it from that dirtbag Owl? See I like a man with a taste in guns. Go get my stash, it's inside the tunnel in Jupiter, where it ends in a concrete mess.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_65">
		<text>The time has come huh? I can't believe I've made it so far. But maybe if there is a fleeting chance for my freedom waged against a stash, go outside and above the tunnel in Jupiter. Then think about it, I will be right here waiting patiently.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_66">
		<text>You whore bitch. My weapon got stuck, if it didn't, it would've been you on your knees. Take my shit, it's in at helipads. Close to the wall in Jupiter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_67">
		<text>Visit a concrete pillar that is located close to heli pads in Jupiter, and you will feel much better for letting me live. Or you could just waste me here and take my stash, but then maybe karma will bite you in the ass and a Controler will fry your brain.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_68">
		<text>I haven't seen you around before, are you new here? You seem to be quite capable with your tools, as it is evident by me kneeling instead of you. As a contribution to your cause, I give you my stash. It is camouflaged in some bushes in the northern quarry, Jupiter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_69">
		<text>I've heard that west of the Jupiter plant, at the very back behind a brick building there is a stash full of the good stuff. How about you doing me a favor now and letting me go?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_70">
		<text>Hey, your gun safety is on! Look... No? Well, at least I tried. Seems to work in movies and computer games. OK I surrender and you can rob my stash that is in the Jupiter plant. On top floor in stairway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_71">
		<text>Ready to visit some scientists?. Go get my stash in the Scientist bunker. in the Southern corner and bring it back to me, then I will decide if I would prefer to let you live.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_88">
		<text>Did you know many interesting people and things happen under the bridge? I've found so many useful things getting washed up from the river. Once I found some denim, perfectly fine after a bit of boiling. Go to the eastern corner in Jupiter, I hid my stash under that bridge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_89">
		<text>I came here with my brother, we got separated when he joined Duty while I was a dedicated Freedom member. Before departing, he told me that if push comes to shove, he stashed some goodies under the bridge, in the western end in Jupiter. It's yours now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_90">
		<text>How about I buy out my life with a nice stash location? Go visit the Jupiter Plant, and walk next to the highest building there. It's close to a tree.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_91">
		<text>No, no, wait. I have things you might use. Don't shoot me, just go get my stash in Jupiter Plant. Outside in the shed. No reason for more violence.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_92">
		<text>I couldn't see it was you, I would never shoot you. We wouldn't be in this situation if I knew it was you. I've seen you around and you look like a decent guy. As a way of apologizing, take my stash. It's in the Jupiter Plant. Top floor, near the stair case.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_93">
		<text>Where there is radiation, no fool would go. Right? Well, not unless you've got 2 bottles of Vodka and a strong will. Malignant tumors to hell right? Just go to the bus in the Jupiter Plant. Inside you will encounter some radiation and my stash. I would advise against eating anything you find there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_94">
		<text>Sneak in the bandit base, or just don't go in blazing. Get up on the top floor. The sleeping room of the main faction is exactly where my stash is. And now you casually let me go right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_72">
		<text>Hey friend, you won't shoot when I'm so friendly to you right? Here, take my stash in Kopatchy Village. Inside grey a brick ruin. It's completely safe there friend, you don't even need to take guns, not even anti-rads or vodka.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_73">
		<text>Pull the fucking trigger, just finish my story because I have nothing for you except my measly stash in Kopatchy Village. Inside a wooden house ruin. But I've heard that radiation has taken residence there, so if you dislike puking your organs one by one for a month, you better be prepared.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_74">
		<text>If you don't pull the trigger, the next time I see you, I will. I won't hesitate like you... Ah you actually want my stash right? It's in Kopatchy Village. Inside the grey concrete ruin. Now piss off or quickly light that canon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_75">
		<text>You seem like a tough bastard, capable, quick to draw the gun, I bet you would rather shoot the mutant that won't fucking leave where I stashed my things, than my beautiful face. Am I right? Eastern tunnel in Jupiter. In the small room. Pack some shot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_76">
		<text>Ever since I was a kid, I had this unhealthy obsession with trains. Back then they ran on gasoline and were filthy as fuck. I used to hang around trains all the time and the pollution there was awful. Now I need money for cancer treatment in Germany. But you don't give three fucks about that. Just go to the Eastern tunnel. On top of the train. I can't go there anymore, because of the mutant.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_77">
		<text>The most sophisticated anti-aircraft system ever devised. That's what they called the Volkov AA Complex. That was naturally all bullshit propaganda. You can gather some loot there since I stashed some of my thing in the large brick building there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_78">
		<text>I've heard that In Jupiter inside the Container Warehouse there is some pretty good loot for the taking. You would rather take that and let me go instead of ending a life right? I have children, two boys and a girl, they don't know I'm here. Check inside the wooden box storages.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_79">
		<text>How about I buy off the bullet you wanted to shoot me with? I've good some good things stashed in the Container Warehouse. Between large some containers. You could certainly handle that. So can I have that bullet? If you fire it, it would be worthless to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_80">
		<text>I've never had to kneel in front of another person before. My father taught me to show respect, and I would be respected. Shooting people isn't very respectful though. To mend our situation here, how about you taking my stash? It's in the Container Warehouse. On the roof of the building in the back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_84">
		<text>Go west of the Container Warehouse, in Jupiter and under some water behind huge rocks you will find what you need. I have nothing else to give.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_85">
		<text>This old bandit had me in a situation similar to what I'm in now, I told him that I didn't have anything. I did not lie, and I won't lie to you now. In a large dead bush west of the Container Warehouse, I keep my stuff. Next time he captures me, I'd have nothing for him once again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_86">
		<text>Tall grass is an excellent camouflage. You could stay there for months near mutants, bandits and mercs, completely hidden. I stashed some of my stuff in high grass next to a tree, on top of the hill. Try finding it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_hiding_place_87">
		<text>Keep your finger off the trigger, you can't use me if I'm dead. Take my stash, it's next to the giant old tree in the bushes.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- PRIPYAT STASHES -->
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_32">
		<text>I've got nothing man, I'm cool now, I won't shoot. I heard about a stash in Pripyat, behind the storage houses in the backyard of Laundromat. But that's all I got man. Can I leave now, is that it?</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_33">
		<text>Old Stalkers talk about Pripyat like it's the Devil's own penthouse. I would never take one step there, but if you happen to get there, get close to the Laundromat and rummage around in some bushes. This is my gift to you, so we can part as friends, and so you don't have to bloody your hands with more death than necessary.</text>
	</string>
			<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_34">
		<text>That ghost town Pripyat sure holds a lot of secrets. One secret I happened to overhear when some old bandits were fighting over the last Vodka bottle. Then they got mauled by a Chimera, and I took flight immediately. I heard them say that the stash is by the steps, next to a stair case leading down.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_35">
		<text>Many buildings in Pipyat have been completely cleaned out by now, whatever they hid before, is long gone now. Remember, Pripyat brings only death and suffering. Search for a stash in these dried out bushes near some red bricked buildings.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_36">
		<text>Pripyat used to be a bustling city, filled with life and energy. Today? All that has been converted into its opposite. There was a few Stalkers that managed to survive there for a while and hid stashes during their stay. Go to the terrace of the Riverport and take what is stashed there, in exchange for my liberty.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_37">
		<text>I intercepted a transmission back when I fiddled with DIY radio, it was strangely from Pripyat. It was of a dying Stalker broadcasting to anyone that is listening to take his stash. Probably because he was breathing through his last moments. You could take it, just go to the top floor of the Apartment Complex. Climb the stairs, it's right there.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_38">
		<text>I have nothing of worth for you. But I do know of a stash in the back room at the gas station in Pripyat, although who the hell would be so suicidal to go there?.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_39">
		<text>Darkness in Pripyat is very different from the darkness you and I are familiar with. It bends your mind, plays tricks on you. Objects begin to move, that don't even exists! But if you are bold enough to go through that, check behind some boxes in a dark room over at Pripyat.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_40">
		<text>I found a big bag full of some notes, I grabbed a few of them and ran since I had a bunch of Fleshes on my back. Most notes were just crazy mumblings, but on one of them a stash was clearly marked. It's on top of crates in good old Pripyat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_41">
		<text>Pripyat is a deadly desert, and for a good reason. It changes you. People come back from there like they've seen the other side of the abyss. But if you are ever unfortunate to go there, go at the back of the Apartment complex and get the stash there.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_42">
		<text>Well, I gave my best shot. Pull the trigger or listen to me carefully about a stash in Pripyat. Visit the Apartment complex. Go to the top floor. Climb some stairs. It's there, don't ask how I know this.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_43">
		<text>Fuck no, not today, please. I was supposed to fucking leave tomorrow. I greased the military at the barricades and everything. Maybe let me be in exchange for a stash location? Go to the Apartment complex in Pripyat, Back room. We ok now?</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_44">
		<text>Please don't do anything to me, I beg of you don't shoot. I was a good person, things forced me in this situation, I did my best. Here, go to the Apartment complex in Pripyat, in the toilets. I overheard some Stalkers joking that nobody would ever check in there for a stash.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_45">
		<text>I surrender, take everything I won't move. I also overheard an exoskeleton equipped Stalker talk of when he was at Pripyat, he hid a stash in the lobby of the Prometheus Movie Theater in Pripyat.</text>
	</string>
			<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_46">
		<text>Stop, I'm unarmed. Don't do it please. I know of this stash, in the hallway close to Prometheus Movie Theater. I know it's Pripyat, so this information isn't worth much to you, but please don't kill me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_47">
		<text>You like being in this position now huh? I'm your bitch now? Well, the "bitch" is worth to you alive more than dead. I know of a stash, its supposed to hold tons of good stuff, but it's in Pripyat, under the iron elephant. Good luck.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_48">
		<text>Keep that gun pointed away from my head. Get to the book store in Pripyat. Top floor holds some nice presents for you. Now leave me be.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_49">
		<text>How about you heading to Pripyat now, instead of having another good person killed for no good reason. There is a stash there next to fireplace inside Prometheus Movie Theater. It's completely safe there, you don't even have to carry any weapons or anything.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_50">
		<text>This is not what I had in mind when I came into this slum pit. After this, I'm going back, fuck curiosity. Go to Pripyat and high above the camp site inside Prometheus Movie Theater you will find a little something for your trouble of letting me go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_51">
		<text>No, NO! They say don't go to Pripyat. Then don't. But if you want my stash, you have to. Peek under the stairs in the Prometheus Movie Theater. Now I will go, I have urgent matters to attend.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_52">
		<text>Pripyat holds many secrets, but not many people know that it also hold many stashes from way back. Check the small room in the kindergarten. If you see children, start running and don't look back until you hit the ocean.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_53">
		<text>Stop that shit right now, get that shooter off my face and I won't call any of my friends to rip your soul out through your throat. Go to the roof of the kindergarten in Pripyat, I'm never going to breathe that stale air again anyway.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_54">
		<text>Inside the Yubileiny Service Center in Pripyat, there is more than meets the eye. Check for a stash there, and let me go my own way.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_55">
		<text>Toilets, nobody checks the toilets. Go to the Yubileiny Service Center and prepare to get your hands dirty. If you survive the trip. Pripyat is where you go if you've got a death wish.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_56">
		<text>They told me never to go to Pripyat. Remains of something evil lays there, and slowly eats away the souls of curious visitors, like rotting flesh. Although someone did go, and stashed his loot there. It's in the Apartment block, behind a stock door leading down.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_57">
		<text>The french came up with the "Art of Displacement", parkour they called it. Came out of military obstacle course training. If you'd like to get your hands on some good loot, and you aren't afraid to look deep inside a void full of unfathomable fears, then go to Pripyat, on the roof of a derelict building.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_58">
		<text>If you already know what dread holds the town of Pripyat, then you might want to know the underground is far worse. Go deep underground, even below the basement and you would get yourself some nice loot to keep you going for a while longer.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_pri_hiding_place_59">
		<text>Pripyat is hell, everyone knows that, but some people did manage to survive there, if only for a short while. They hid a stash there, it's cleverly hidden right under the roof. That should change your mind about blowing my brains out right?</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
